RHAGAVIT

Erode, India 638008 ◆ 9843273233 ◆ Rhagavi3@gmail.com

LINKEDIN, PORTFOLIO

- www.linkedin.com/in/rhagavi
- https://6300d91e37e9f842526db1f5friendly-wisp-2f2549.netlify.app/

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Technically Sophisticated Professional with almost 5 years of experience in the areas of Software Development, Team Management, and Support Analyst. Exposure to both frontend and backend technologies (MERN). Experience in executing projects involving: REST API integration/creation,

Skills

- Programming Languages: JavaScript.
- Tools: GIT
- Frameworks: Express JS, React JS, Node JS
- Databases: MYSQL, Mongo DB

- Cloud: AWS
- Operating Systems: Windows
- CSS: Material UI, Bootstrap 5, Chakra UI, React-Font Awesome UI
- LIBRARIES-React Redux, Socket.IO

CERTIFICATIONS

 Certified MERN STACK DEVELOPER GUVI GEEKS PRIVATE LIMITED - APRIL 2022-NOV 2022 (IIT MADRAS)

Work Experience -

Systems Engineer, 12/2017 to Current **INFOSYS LIMITED** – CHENNAI, India

- Develop and Support respective clients.
- Collaborated with executive team to define business requirements and systems goals.
- Install, configure, test and maintain operating systems, application software and system management tools.

Clients

1)AVON

- Debugged JSON data after development and fix bugs and errors on time.
- Debug XML errors and handle release process smoothly.
- Verify and grant access to client users of Avon.
- Managed maximum 5 production releases in day.

2)Walmart Support Systems(May 2018-Jan 2019)

- Provided resolutions and handled critical resolutions for Walmart users.
- Worked in SQL and debugged data.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.

3) Royal Bank of scotland (April 2019-Dec 2019)

- Got trained as JavaScript developer and worked on small tasks during development.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.

4) Royal Bank of Scotland (Jan 2020-Jun 2020)

- Worked with fast migration for internal team and convinced clients by explaining process and handled process smoothly.
- Analyzed key aspects of business to evaluate factors driving results and summarized into presentations.
- Applied honed problem-solving skills to analyze and resolve issues impacting business operations and goal achievement.

Operations Executive Trainee, 12/2017 to 04/2018
Infosys Limited – Mysore, India

TRAINED IN

- Javascript, SQL, Java
- Used coordination and planning skills to achieve results according to schedule

EDUCATION -

MCA: Masters in Computer Applications, 05/2022 **Bharathiyar University** - Coimbatore, Tamilnadu

BCA: COMPUTER APPLICATIONS, 04/2017 **Kongu Arts And Science** - Erode, TamilNadu